44 Mandelbulb3D colours and lights.

*     *     *     *
Just put .m3l files in Mandelbulb3D folder and start the program.

*     *     *     *

I made this collection after I realised that there is not much publicly aviable colour files unless you do them by yourself, and that after finding good fractal spot it's pretty easy to just slice colours and look, which fitts the best. 

All metalic colours starts with metal_ , but there are additional colours with pretty metalic shine. They works better with fractals having smooth surface.

Colour palettes are derived from different sources, some are my original creations, some are other peoples colours, but wast majority are ultimately traced back to Fractint public collection, both directly or via Chaos Pro. As in Fractint all visual effects depends solelly on premade colour palettes, it have quite a few atmospheric time tested colour files like reptilian "dragon" or bunch of gradients simulating metallic shine. 
Metallic_cloud (good after hard shadows) is saved from user Kali shared spot, StalagmitesAndStalagtites1.m3l were shared by user Lalla, Ikmitch_tangerine.m3l is M3D adaptation of Ikmitch Ultra Fractal gradient of shared spots, Ukrainian.m3l is adapted Fractal Explorer standart gradient. Tree_wood.m3l, Summer_Nights.m3l and Moon_Shine.m3l come from example parameter files, all are included with a purpose that colours would be enought different.

by Edgar Malinovsky 14.08.2012.

p.s.
Colours are never too much.